(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
YouTube Music Weekendをご覧の皆さん、こんにちは！
YouTube Music Weekend viewers, hello!
こんにちはー！
Hello!
It's the Top, We Are ReGLOSS!
ホロライブデバイスのReGLOSSです。
We are ReGLOSS from Hololive DEV_IS.
YouTube Music Weekendをご覧の方は、私たちのことをご存じない方も
To those watching YouTube Music Weekend, there may be some who don't know us...
いるかもしれないので、一人ずつ自己紹介から行きたいと思います！
So we'd like to start with self-introductions from each of us!
イェーイ！
Yay!
じゃあ奏から！
Then, starting with Kanade!
はい！ドレミファソラシド...
Yes! Do-Re-Mi-Fa-So-La-Ti-Do...
ホロライブデバイス所属、ReGLOSSの音楽家、音乃瀬奏です！
From Hololive DEV_IS, ReGLOSS's musician, Otonose Kanade!
イェーイ！
Yay!
そして...
And next...
はい！可愛いポジティブジーニアス...
Yes! The cute positive genius...
ホロライブデバイスReGLOSSの一条莉々華だよ！みんなヤッホー元気？
Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS's Ichijou Lirika! Everyone, yoo-hoo, how are you?
元気だよー！
We're doing great!
そして！
And!
はーい！皆さんこんにちは。
Hi! Hello everyone.
ホロライブデバイスReGLOSSの賑やかしネタ枠担当、儒烏風亭らでん...
Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS's boisterous jokester role, Juufuutei Raden...
前座見習い、巻竹ぐるぐるのお姉さんこと儒烏風亭らでんでございます。どうも。
Opening act apprentice, the "swirling bamboo scroll" lady, Juufuutei Raden. Hello.
巻竹、巻竹、ぐるぐるぐるぐる...
Bamboo scroll, bamboo scroll, swirling, swirling...
そして！
And!
パンパンパパパーン！ホロライブデバイスReGLOSSの...
Bang bang bang! Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS's...
パン、轟はじめ！
Bang, Todoroki Hajime!
パン、パン、パパーン！
Bang, bang, bang!
いや、去年に引き続き、今年もYouTube Music Weekendに参加させていただけて...
Well, following last year, being able to participate in YouTube Music Weekend again this year...
ちょっと甘噛みした今！
You just bit your tongue!
これ何？逃さないよ今！
What's this? I won't let that slide!
可愛がっちゃう。
How cute.
今、いいに行けるかなと思っちゃった。じゃあもう一回！もう一回行かせて！
I thought I could push through. Okay, one more time! Let me try again!
ふぅー、去年に引き続き、今年もYouTube Music Weekendに参加させていただけて光栄です！
Phew... following last year, I am honored to participate in YouTube Music Weekend again this year!
やったー！
Yay!
え、みんな去年、何の曲やったか覚えてる？
Hey, does everyone remember what songs we performed last year?
シンメトリー！
Symmetry!
あ、シンメトリーやったねー！
Ah, we did perform "Symmetry"!
瞬間ハートビートもやったっちょと思う！
I think we also performed "Shunkan Heartbeat"!
絶対やったよ！デビュー曲だもんね！
We definitely did! It's our debut song!
そして...
And...
うん、そしてもう一曲やってて、当時の新曲である『泡沫Baby』も披露させていただきました！
Yeah, and we did one more song, our new song at the time, "Utakata Baby"!
わあ、懐かしい！
Wow, how nostalgic!
ね、本当に懐かしいね。
Right, it's really nostalgic.
すごいもう、超昔のことのように思えるし、当時はね、こういうステージに立つわけじゃなくって...
It feels like such a long time ago, and back then, we weren't standing on a stage like this...
こう何ていうか、あの、周り見てこれ。すごくない？
It's like, look around at this. Isn't it amazing?
お客さんがいる！すごい！ありがとう！
There's an audience! Incredible! Thank you!
ちょっとみんな浸んとしないで！
Hey, don't get all quiet on me!
大丈夫、画面の向こうでは今めっちゃ盛り上がってくれてると思う。
It's okay, I'm sure everyone behind their screens is really excited right now.
真剣に見ちゃってんのか！おめでとうだよ！
Maybe they're just watching intently! Congratulations!
すごいね、カメラとかステージとかも進化して、再び戻ってきちゃいました！
It's amazing how the cameras and stage have evolved, and here we are back again!
すごーい！
Amazing!
実はね、昨年から楽曲も増えまして...
Actually, we've had more songs since last year...
今年はね、3月に『さくらミラージュ』、7月に『ミッドサマーストラス』という曲をリリースしてあります！
This year, we released "Sakura Mirage" in March and "Midsummer Citrus" in July!
あります！
We did!
いや、また今年もこうして新しい曲を皆さんに披露することができて嬉しいね！
I'm so happy to be able to perform our new songs for everyone again this year!
ねー、嬉しい！
Yeah, it's great!
そしてそして、実は8月に、なななななんと！奏たちのソロ曲を毎週連続リリースしてました！
And and, actually, in August, can you believe it? We released solo songs every week!
イェーイ！
Yay!
らっちゃんから！
Starting with Raden!
はい、らでんです。らでんのソロ曲『お落とし咄』リリースさせていただきました。
Hi, I'm Raden. I released my solo song, "Otoshi Banashi".
なんと語りあり、言葉遊びあり、ラップありと、らでんらしさをギュッと詰め込んだ楽曲となっております。
It's a song packed with my style, featuring narration, wordplay, and even rap.
そしてね、実はこの要素も...
And actually, this element too...
え、ホロライブ？
Eh, Hololive?
どっかにあったりするんですけども！
It's in there somewhere!
気づかなかった！
I didn't notice!
あるんですね、実は。ちょっと探して聞いてみようかなーなんて。
It's actually there. Maybe I'll try to find it and listen for it.
ぜひ『お落とし咄』よろしくお願いします。そして、らでんの次の週にリリースしたのだーれだ？
Please check out "Otoshi Banashi". And who released theirs the week after mine?
はーい！奏！
Me! Kanade!
奏は『Cheerful Vibes Echo』という楽曲を...
Kanade released a song called "Cheerful Vibes Echo"...
発音が良すぎてなんて言ったの？
Your pronunciation was too good, what did you say?
『Cheerful Vibes Echo』という楽曲をリリースしました！
"Cheerful Vibes Echo"! I released that song!
こちらの楽曲はですね、ちょっとアコギがジャンジャカジャンジャカする感じの曲で
This song has an acoustic guitar that goes "jang-jaka-jang-jaka"...
何かすごいね、しっとりとした曲で、朝とかに起きて聞くと...
...and it's a very mellow song that, if you listen to it when you wake up in the morning...
「はぁ、今日もいい朝だな。頑張ろう」ってなる曲をですね、作らせていただきまして。
..."Ah, it's a good morning. I'll do my best today," it makes you feel like that.
奏もすごいニコニコしながら歌ったので、元気が出る、そういう楽曲になっています。
I sang it with a big smile, so it's a song that gives you energy.
よかったら聴いてね！
Please give it a listen!
聴いてね！
Give it a listen!
そして奏の次はだーれだ？
And who came after Kanade?
はーい！莉々華の楽曲！
Me! Lirika's song!
タイトルが『ハピネスフェノメノン』！
The title is "Happiness Phenomenon"!
「いい女」がもう全身から溢れ出ちゃうような、そんな楽曲になっていて...
It's a song where "a fine woman" just overflows from my entire being...
もう聴くだけで気分アゲアゲ、自己肯定感アゲアゲな楽曲となってます。
...and just listening to it gets your mood and self-esteem way up.
朝とかお昼とか、これから頑張るぞ！みたいな時に聴いてね、一緒に元気を出してもらえたらいいなと思っております！たくさん聴いてねー！
In the morning or at lunch, when you're ready to go, please listen to it and get energized! Listen to it a lot!
見ててください！
Please watch!
あー、最後は夜明けから始まるソロ曲『ビビデバビデ』でした！
Ah, and finally, my solo song 'Bibide Babide' starts from the dawn!
何でー！？
Wait, why!?
ビビデバビデだ！
It's Bibide Babide!
ビビデバビデ！
Bibide Babide!
ソロ曲なんですけど...
It's a solo song, but...
すごいダンスナンバーで、こう...
it's a high-energy dance number, where...
ドゥンドゥンって鳴る低音が、こう、ズンズンなってて...
the bass goes 'doon doon', thumping like this...
なんかサビに音がちょっと少ないんだけど...
the sound is a bit sparse in the chorus...
静かな静寂の中で、ドゥン、ドゥン、ドゥン、って...
in the quiet stillness, it goes 'thump, thump, thump'...
ちょっとノった感じの。私、結構ダウナーなんですけど...
it's got a groove to it. I'm usually quite a downer...
その、夜のちょっとダウナーな、静かな感じと...
that nighttime, slightly downer, quiet vibe...
その低音のドゥンドゥンっていうカッコ良さが合わさった曲になってて。
and that cool, heavy bass combined in one song.
なんかこう、夜にちょっと、あ～って...
It's like something you listen to at night and just...
あ～聴きたい！
Oh, I want to hear it!
一人で聴いてほしいなって。
I want you to listen to it alone.
ラップとかダンスブレイクもあって...
There's also rap and a dance break...
すごいカッコいい曲になってるので、ぜひ聴いてください！
it's a really cool song, so please listen to it!
聴いてください！
Please listen!
実はあれなんだよね、ソロ曲それぞれ...
Actually, the thing is, each of our solo songs...
時間帯が変わっていくんだよね。
represents a different time of day.
あ、そうだね。
Oh, that's right.
らでんが夜明け前で...
Raden's is before dawn...
奏が朝！
Kanade's is morning!
リリカがお昼！
Ririka's is noon!
はじめ夜！
Hajime's is night!
そう！
Yes!
この順に聴くと、さらに深みが増すんじゃないかなと。
If you listen to them in this order, it might add more depth.
確かに。
True.
という感じでね...
So, in that way...
ReGLOSSのみんなの個性が詰まった楽曲になってるので。
each song is filled with the personality of ReGLOSS.
概要欄にリンクが貼ってありますので。
There are links in the description box.
そちらもぜひ聴いてみてください！
So please check those out too!
聴いてねー！
Listen to them!
MC長いよ、って思われてるかもしれないけど...
You might be thinking this talk segment is too long...
思ってないよ！
They're not!
もうちょいだけ喋らせて。この後すぐに歌うので。
Let us talk just a bit more. We'll sing right after.
あとちょっとね、待っててね。
Wait just a little longer, okay?
しかもですね、私たち今年の9月で...
What's more, this September...
なんとデビュー2周年を迎えます！
we'll celebrate our 2nd anniversary!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
嘘！？
Really!?
そう。デビュー2周年を迎えるということは？
Yes. And reaching our 2nd anniversary means...?
お、何？
Oh, what?
3Dの記念配信もあるということ！
That there's going to be a 3D anniversary stream!
初めて聞いた！
First time I've heard that!
9月13日の土曜日に...
On Saturday, September 13th...
3D記念配信があります！
there will be a 3D anniversary stream!
9月13日(土) 20時「ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary」
September 13th (Sat) 20:00 "ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary"
何するのー？
What are you doing?
歌ったり、踊ったりしちゃうんじゃない？
Won't we be singing and dancing?
漫才じゃないんですか？番長だけが踊る...
Isn't it comedy? Where only Bancho dances...
何で！？みんなで歌って踊ろうよ！
Why!? Let's all sing and dance together!
え～どうしようかな。
Hmm, what should we do?
何でみんな驚いてるの。
Why is everyone so surprised?
やるんでしょ？やんなよ！
We're doing it, right? Do it!
漫才かなと思って。
I thought it was comedy.
漫才じゃないよ。
It's not comedy.
冗談はさておき、この2年間練習も重ねてきたので。
Jokes aside, we've been practicing for two years.
みんなに見てもらうために。
So everyone can see us.
去年よりもパワーアップした姿をお見せしたいなと。
We want to show you how much we've improved since last year!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ちなみに、この1年で変わったこととかある？
By the way, has anything changed for you this past year?
変わったこと...
Changed things...
何もかも変わったけどね。
Everything has changed.
奏は結構変わったのあるって。
Kanade, you have some big changes.
ま、レッスンとかね。1周年の時にやって...
Well, lessons. During our 1st anniversary live...
踊りながら歌うのって、大変だなってすごい思って。
I really felt that singing while dancing is tough.
立って歌うのだったら、得意なのかなと思ってたけど。
I thought I was good at singing while standing still.
体を動かしながらだと、息が上がっちゃって難しくて。
But moving my body makes me out of breath and it's hard.
そこからボイトレとかダンスレッスンを増やして。
So I increased my vocal training and dance lessons.
奏はかなり発声が変わりました！
Actually, my vocalization has changed a lot!
おー！
Whoa!
歌上手だったのに、よりグレードアップしたんだね！
You were already good, but you've upgraded even more!
さらに、さらに。
Even more, even more.
パワーアップしたので、見比べてみてください。
She's powered up, so please compare the difference.
見てください！これからも進化するぞー！
Please watch! I'll keep evolving!
流石、歌柱。歌柱じゃない、歌バシラ。
As expected of the Song Pillar. No, Utabashira.
歌バシラは本家の人。ヤバいヤバい。
Utabashira is someone else. Oh no, oh no.
はじめもダンスの、新しいジャンルに挑戦したくて。
I also wanted to try a new dance genre.
それを今年、2つチャレンジしてて。
I'm challenging two new ones this year.
一つは、言ってるタップなんだけど。
One is the tap dancing I mentioned.
もう一個も、別のジャンルを初めてみてたりしてて。
The other is a different genre I'm trying for the first time.
超全然違うから、本当ゼロからのスタートみたいな。
It's totally different, so it's like starting from zero.
だから、また3Dライブとかで披露できる時に...
So when I have the chance to perform at a 3D live...
また進化した姿を見せられるんじゃないかなと。
I hope to show you an evolved version of myself.
楽しみー！
Looking forward to it!
二人は得意なことをさらにグレードアップしたんだね。
So you two upgraded the things you're good at.
頑張ってるってことだよね
That means you're working hard.
ねー！
Yeah!
はい、莉々華は、あの、ちょっと心持ちが変わったなって思ってることがあって
Yes, as for me, Ririka, there's something that I feel has changed in my mindset.
最初、本当にちょっとダンスが、特に苦手すぎて
At first, I was really just too bad at dancing in particular.
こういうライブとか、みんなの前で踊るみたいなときに、緊張だったりとか不安だったりがいっぱいあったんだけど
When it came to lives like this or dancing in front of everyone, I had a lot of nervousness and anxiety.
まぁ今回、とある曲を、踊らせていただいて、歌わせていただいたんですけど
But this time, I had the chance to dance and sing a certain song.
それを撮ったときに
When we recorded that,
なんか、不安だなって気持ちより、一緒にやってて楽しいなっていう気持ちのほうがなんかあった気がして
I felt like I had more of a feeling of "this is fun to do together" than "I'm anxious."
えー！嬉しいー！
Whoa! I'm so happy!
えー、嬉しいって思った
Yeah, I thought, "I'm happy."
あら素敵じゃない、奥さん素敵よ、あなた
Oh, how wonderful. Ma'am, you're wonderful.
それ聞けたらこっちも嬉ちいよな
Hearing that makes us happy too.
ねえ！やったー！よかったねー！
Right! Yay! That's great!
これからもいっぱい歌って踊って、レッスンも頑張っていきたいと思います！
I want to keep singing and dancing a lot and work hard in lessons!
頑張ろ頑張ろ頑張ろ
Let's do our best, let's do our best!
らでんちゃんは？
How about you, Raden-chan?
らでんさ、作詞にはまってさ、この1年で
Well, I've gotten into writing lyrics this past year.
で、自分でね、特にラップ？
And for myself, especially rap?
やっぱね、言葉が好きなのよね、特に日本語が好きで
I just love words, you know. I especially love the Japanese language.
で、それでちょっと何かやりたいなと思って、自作のラップ書いて、自分のチャンネルに投稿したりとか
So I wanted to do something with that, and I wrote my own rap and posted it on my channel.
ねえ素敵だったよね！私たちの名前とかも入れてくれて
Hey, that was wonderful! You even included our names.
そうそうそう！言葉遊びがいっぱい！
Right, right, right! Lots of wordplay!
そう、なんかそういうね、言葉と音楽みたいなところで、自分の中で新しいチャレンジができたかなという1年でしたね
Yeah, so it was a year where I think I was able to take on new challenges in that area of words and music.
すごーい！
Amazing!
もうみんなそれぞれにね、成長と挑戦を重ねた1年でございましたと
It's been a year where each of us has had our share of growth and challenges.
ございました！
Indeed!
でもね、まだまだね、伸び代もあるし、成長できる部分いっぱいあると思うから、これからも頑張ってこうね！
But you know, we still have room to grow and plenty of areas to improve, so let's keep working hard!
頑張ろー！ダンス頑張るよー！
Let's do it! I'll work hard on my dancing!
はい！ということで今回は、先日発表されました、私たちReGLOSSの新曲「MID-SUMMER ASTRAS」をこの後披露させていただきます！
Yes! So today, we're going to perform our new ReGLOSS song that was announced the other day, "MID-SUMMER ASTRAS"!
イェーイ！
Yay!
3月にリリースした「さくらミラージュ」は、春の訪れを感じられる楽曲だったと思いますが
Our song "Sakura Mirage," released in March, was a track that made you feel the arrival of spring.
今回の「MID-SUMMER ASTRAS」は、タイトル通り、タイトル通り...
But this "MID-SUMMER ASTRAS" is, as the title suggests... as the title suggests...
夏！！
Summer!!
暑っ！ふーや、熱！
Hot! Phew, it's hot!
今これステージ立ってるけど日陰とかないからね！
We're standing on stage right now, but there's no shade!
もう日焼けやばいって！
This sunburn is going to be terrible!
でもやっぱ、こうReGLOSSが夏と一緒にここに帰ってきたっていう感じするよね！
But it really feels like ReGLOSS has come back here along with the summer!
爽やかなメロディとね、心地よいリズムが夏の暑さを吹き飛ばしてくれるような一曲になってます！
It's a song with a refreshing melody and a pleasant rhythm that'll blow away the summer heat!
どんどん！で、みんなこの曲のイメージとか、なんかレコーディングのエピソードとかある？
Boom boom! So, does anyone have an image of this song or any recording episodes?
やっぱ夏だしすごい爽やかな曲だから、明るく楽しく爽やかにっていうのをすごいイメージしながら歌ったの覚えてる
Since it's summer and a very refreshing song, I remember singing it while really imagining being bright, fun, and refreshing.
あーいいいね！
Oh, that's nice!
確かにそんな感じだった！
It certainly felt like that!
はいはい、奏ちゃんはどう？
Yes, yes. How about you, Kanade-chan?
この楽曲のサビに、「踊ってミッドサマー」っていうフレーズがあるんだけど
In the chorus of this song, there's a phrase that goes "Odotte Midsummer."
歌うま！凄腕、歌うま出た今。
You're good at singing! Wow, such a talented singer just now.
ありがと
Thanks.
そのサンバをさ、かなで凄いリズムノリノリに乗るの好きだから
I really like getting into the groove of that samba rhythm.
「踊ってミッドサマー！」ってやってさ、「サンバ！」ってあんまりになっちゃった？
So when I did "Odotte Midsummer!", did I end up going a bit too "Samba!"?
わかったわかった。
I get it, I get it.
ディレクターさんにね、お歌をやってくれるディレクターさんに、「いや、ちょっとサンバすぎるんで、ちょっと普通に歌ってください」って言われて
The director, the one in charge of the vocals, told me, "Um, that's a bit too much samba, so please just sing it normally."
調整して歌ったの覚えてます
I remember adjusting and singing it.
めっちゃいいエピソードあるやん
That's a great episode.
初めて聞いたよそれ、うちらにも話したことなかったじゃんそれ
That's the first time I've heard that. You hadn't even told us that.
あと振付で好きなとこがあって
Also, there's a part of the choreography I like.
やっぱサビのみんな好きやと思うけど、サビのここ！
I think everyone likes the chorus, but this part of the chorus!
「踊ってミッドサマー」あの「ギコギコ」って覚えてる？
"Odotte Midsummer," that "Giko Giko" part, do you remember?
紐でギコギコ、
Sawing with a string,
あ、なるほどね！
Oh, I see!
これが楽しくてめっちゃ好き！
This is so fun, I love it!
気持ちいいもんね、ここ、バシッとハマるよね！
It feels good, doesn't it? It clicks right into place!
らでんちゃんはどう？
How about you, Raden-chan?
いっぱい練習しました！聞いてください！
I practiced a lot! Please listen!
もうダンスも歌もとにかく大変でした、いっぱい聞いてください！
Both the dancing and singing were just so tough. Please listen to it a lot!
はい、じゃあそんな「MID-SUMMER ASTRAS」、この後みんなに見てもらおうと思うけど
All right, then, we're about to show everyone "MID-SUMMER ASTRAS."
もう早く見てもらいたいよね！そろそろね、MCだいぶ長くなってきちゃったしね！
But we want you to see it as soon as possible! Besides, this MC segment is getting pretty long!
やったー！
We did it!
どうしよう、これ。
What should we do with this?
じゃあ...
Well then...
はい！では皆さんにもね、一緒に楽しんでもらえればと思います。
Yes! Well then, I hope everyone can enjoy it together with us.
いきますよ！
Here we go!
うん！
Yeah!
それでは、どうぞー！
And now, please enjoy!
ミッドサマーシトラス
作詞：OHTORA　作曲：OHTORA / messhime soshi
編曲：messhime soshi
Midsummer Citrus
Lyrics: OHTORA  Composition: OHTORA / messhime soshi
Arrangement: messhime soshi
氷解くような日差し
Sunlight that seems to melt ice
水面に浮かぶバンカー
Bunkers floating on the water surface
はしゃぐ夏色と逆光の裏側で
Behind the frolicking summer colors and the backlight
あの日の青春を呼び起こしてる
Awakening the youth of that day
目にものすさまじく舞って
Dancing intensely before my eyes
裸足で走ってる砂の上
Running barefoot on the sand
ガラスの縁で回り回るガムシャラ
Struggling as it spins on the edge of the glass
くるり彩のビー玉
A spinning colored marble
なんだかその笑顔と神一重だ
Somehow, it's a hair's breadth away from that smile
フィルムを覗けばもうフィクション
Looking through the film, it's already fiction
彩りに反射されたメモリー
Memories reflected in various colors
リセットなんてできないから
Because you can't just reset it
Love yourself I's you and now
踊ってミッドサマー アルゴリズムの中
Dance, midsummer, within the algorithm
瞬速でダビングして
Dubbing in an instant
切り取ってきっと愛だ これがきっと愛だ
Cutting it out, it's surely love, this is surely love
二度と忘れないように
So I'll never forget it again
Lemon Lime Orange 君と一緒の思い出
Lemon Lime Orange, memories together with you
何気ない一日がワンダーバケーション
An ordinary day is a wonder vacation
氷が溶けては渦巻いた
Ice melted and swirled
魔法の杖代わりのマドラー
A muddler instead of a magic wand
喉の奥くすぐる炭酸
Carbonation tickling the back of my throat
香る柑橘系の平和
The peace of citrus scents
爽やかな気流に乗って
Riding on a refreshing airstream
波の帰りを身守ってるビーチ
The beach watching over the return of the waves
あどけない面影に焦がれ
Yearning for that innocent look
霞むレンズ そらす指先
Hazy lens, averting fingertips
きらめいて上塗りした今
The present, sparkling and painted over
Get the hell what you used to be
踊ってミッドサマー アルゴリズムの中
Dance, midsummer, within the algorithm
瞬速でダビングして
Dubbing in an instant
切り取ってきっと愛だ これがきっと愛だ
Cutting it out, it's surely love, this is surely love
二度とは忘れないように
So I'll never forget it again
ミッドサマーシトラス Oh Yeah
Midsummer Citrus Oh Yeah
いつだって We gonna be okay
Always We gonna be okay
見ているだけでピース 眩しい心はまた実り
Just looking at it is peace, my dazzling heart bears fruit again
寝起きの太陽を願ってもない燦々日和
Wishing for the sun upon waking, on a brilliantly sunny day
色褪せてしまうほど眩しいの夏の日
A summer day so dazzling it might fade away
踊ってミッドサマー アルゴリズムの中
Dance, midsummer, within the algorithm
瞬速でダビングして
Dubbing in an instant
切り取ってきっと愛だ これがきっと愛だ
Cutting it out, it's surely love, this is surely love
二度とは忘れないように
So I'll never forget it again
Lemon Lime Orange 君と一緒の思い出
Lemon Lime Orange, memories together with you
何気ない一日がワンダーバケーション
An ordinary day is a wonder vacation